// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The Local Government Council is entitled with the role of: ",
    answer:
      "control and regulation of movement and keeping of pets of all kinds",
    options: [
      "Scattering of thugs, louts, and touts in the commmunity",
      "control and regulation of movement and keeping of pets of all kinds",
      "appointment of youths as OPC members",
      "Serving as watchdog for the government",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Your Right to ____ is the most crucial ?",
    answer: "The right to live",
    options: [
      "The right to freedom of association",
      "The right to independence",
      "The right to live",
      "The right to speech",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question:
      "As per right to freedom of expression, there are certain constraints which one of them is ?",
    answer: "Hate Speech",
    options: [
      "When the Citizen is a criminal",
      "Hate Speech",
      "When in Quarantine",
      "There are no constraints",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "When is the constitution made ?",
    answer: "1999",
    options: ["1999", "1967", "1973", "2004"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The House of Assembly can only speak in English?",
    answer: "Not only, but as well as Yoruba, Ibo, and Hausa",
    options: [
      "Yes, only in English",
      "Not only, but as well as French, and Pidgin",
      "Merely any language that deems fit for the House of Assembly",
      "Not only, but as well as Yoruba, Ibo, and Hausa",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "If the federation is at war, the 4 years tenure is extended to?",
    answer: "A maximum of 6 months",
    options: [
      "A maximum of 6 months",
      "Another duration of 4 years",
      "The national assembly will sit to decide",
      "The war determines the tenure",
    ],
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The legislative has the power to conduct investigation",
    answer: "Yes, on the basis to make and ammend laws",
    options: [
      "That's a duty of the police",
      "Yes, on the basis to make and ammend laws",
      "That;s a duty of the Private/Public Investigators",
      "Absolutely Not!",
    ],
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question:
      "A member of the House of Assembly is free to join any political party of his/her choice even when his current party's tenure is still valid",
    answer:
      "No, for upon joining, he will be disqualified as a member of the Assembly",
    options: [
      "Yes, his/her political right stands still",
      "He/She willl need to go through some procedures to achieve this",
      "No, for upon joining, he will be disqualified as a member of the Assembly",
      "Yes, The matter will be tabled before the National Assembly, and it's until the National Assembly's approval",
    ],
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question:
      "All public office holders including the governor, its vice, president, etc.. are ?",
    answer: "Not entitled to have a foreign account",
    options: [
      "Not entitled to have a foreign account",
      "To be offered gifts and presents to thank them for their service",
      "To be either Christians or Muslims",
      "To be friends and act as one family",
    ],
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Who has the right to deport non-citizens",
    answer: "The Legislative body",
    options: [
      "The President",
      "The House of Assembly",
      "The Legislative body",
      "The Executive body",
    ],
  },

  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Farming is regarded as a 'business' as well?",
    answer:
      "No, farming alone is excluded by what is meant by business in the law",
    options: [
      "Yes, in my perspective",
      "No, farming alone is excluded by what is meant by business in the law",
      "Maybe",
      "I guess so",
    ],
  },

  {
    numb: 12,
    question:
      "In Nigeria's Oath of Alligence, there are three things sworn about, which are?",
    answer: "To preserve, protect, and defend",
    options: [
      "Obey, Perform duties, Ask for rights",
      "To pretend, present, and deceive",
      "To preserve, protect, and defend",
      "To learn, educate, and work",
    ],
  },

  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "House of Assembly is established ?",
    answer: "For every states of the federation",
    options: [
      "For every states of the federation",
      "At the capital of the federation, Abuja",
      "In some popular states in the federation",
      "As wished by the President",
    ],
  },

  {
    numb: 14,
    question:
      "Right to not perform forced labour is not restricted in communities as well?",
    answer:
      "No, the right is restricted in well-being communities, where our tribes falls in",
    options: [
      "Yes, parents are not to force children to perform labour",
      "Yes, communities are to ensure that no one is to perform forced labour",
      "No, the right is restricted in well-being communities, where our tribes falls in",
      "The parents decides",
    ],
  },

  {
    numb: 15,
    question:
      "You do have the right to decide if your photos are to be taken or not?",
    answer:
      "Yes, for without your permission, the performer of thr action is iable to prosecution",
    options: [
      "Anyone has the right to do as they like",
      "I don't think that does any harm",
      "Yes, for without my permission, the performer of the action is liable to prosecution",
      "If the person is not a relative or known individual",
    ],
  },
];
